OPERATIONS/OFFICE MANAGER

Objective

A highly organized and detail-oriented Executive Assistant with over 13 years' experience providing thorough and skillful administrative support to senior executives, with strong customer service and project coordination background. Professional Highlights Twistory Studios Facility management/office expansion build-out Tradeshow coordination for multiple events throughout the US (including Comic-Con San Diego and Comic-Con NY) Responsible for all Human Resources functionality for office (recruitment, training, payroll, development of employee policy/handbook, emergency action protocol) KB Home National Supplier Conference Event planning/coordination for multi-day (off-site) event \hat{a} 6ceSoup to Nuts \hat{a} 6 planning for 100+ senior executives Came in \$10k - \$20k under budget for event annually Skills

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Project Management
- Payroll
- Event Planning
- Insurance Certifications Travel/Calendar Coordination
- Expense Reports
- Multi-line telephone systems
- Human Resources (Recruiting/Training)
- Customer Service
- Bartender/Sales Canter's Deli, Los Angeles, CA 2015 Present
- Beauty Advisor/Sales Macy's/Nordstrom, Los Angeles, CA 2014 2015
- Operations/Office Manager Twistory Studios, Santa Monica, CA 2012 2013
- Executive Assistant Activision, Santa Monica, CA 2009 2010
- International Coordinator/Executive Assistant Davis Langdon, Santa Monica, CA 2008 -
- 2009
- Executive Assistant KB Home, Los Angeles, CA 2002 2008

- Procedure development
- Personable
- Team building
- Multi-site operations Inventory control
- Staff retention
- Contract management
- Relationship building
- Client relationships
- Articulate and well-spoken
- Time management
- Invoice processing
- Works well under pressure
- Social media knowledge
- Travel administration
- Self-starter
- Workers' compensation knowledge

Accomplishments

• Task Force Member - KB Home Community Support/Fundraising Efforts Coordination/procurement of donation items from staff and vendors Team lead for task force members /liaison with donation recipient contacts Helped provide gifts to 100+ recipients for various recipients annually (Children's Hospital of Los Angeles, Simi Valley Battered Women's Shelter, Project Angel Food) Davis Langdon Executive Leadership Conference (US Board Members) "Soup to Nuts†planning for 24 Board Members (3 months to plan event) Coordinated Team Building exercises with off-site vendors Came in \$7k under budget Team Building - Activision Initiated quarterly team BBOs/lunches for Studio Group.

Experience

Cavco Industries Phoenix, OR Operations/Office Manager 02/2012 to 05/2013 Developed and shared best practices across the company, including Emergency Awareness Preparedness and Employee Handbook. Recruited, hired and trained 30 - 35 new employees for various departments within the studio. Identified inefficiencies and made recommendations for process improvements.

American Express District Of Columbia, DC Executive Assistant - WW Studios 02/2009 to 08/2010 Arranged appropriate travel, visas, agendas, necessary contacts and country information. Maintained and coordinated executive and senior management vacation, day-to-day meeting and travel schedules. Collaborated with other administrative team members, human resources and the finance department on special projects and events. Provided logistical support to visiting executives in coordination with other Executive Assistants. Handled and distributed all incoming and outgoing mail. Wrote and distributed meeting minutes to appropriate individuals. Created and maintained computer- and paper-based filing and organization systems for records, reports and documents.

KB Home City, STATE Executive Assistant 05/2002 to 05/2008 Served as Executive Assistant to the VP, National Contracts and senior team leaders. Approved travel expenses and reimbursement requests. Initiated and updated yearly dealer agreements and dealer applications. Investigated issues and problems and drafted responses to urgent requests. Created and maintained computer- and paper-based filing and organization systems for records, reports and documents. Open, read, and wrote answers to routine letters. Wrote and distributed meeting minutes to appropriate individuals. Provided logistical support to visiting executives in coordination with other Executive Assistants. Collaborated with other administrative team members, human resources and the finance department on special projects and events. Maintained and coordinated executive and senior management vacation, day-to-day meeting and travel schedules. Arranged appropriate travel, visas, agendas, necessary contacts and country information. Drafted meeting agendas, supplied advance materials and executed follow-up for meetings and team conferences. Maintained an up-to-date department organizational chart. Maintained and reserved the executive conference room calendar. Managed daily office operations and maintenance of equipment.

Education and Training

AA: Liberal Arts May 1991 Allan Hancock College , City , State Liberal Arts Skills

CA, Customer Service, Event Planning, Expense Reports, Human Resources, Insurance, Microsoft Office Suite, Multi-line telephone, Office Manager, Payroll, Project Management, Recruiting, Sales